Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
=In The Name of Loyalty=
=باسم الولاء=
=Episode 5=
=الحلقة 5=
Stop.
قف.
You,
أنت،
get in.
أدخل.
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I mean the Empress.
أقصد الإمبراطورة.
I didn't expect
لم اتوقع
you to be that clever
أنت ذكي للغاية
to fool her.
لخداعها.
Just a delaying tactic.
إنها مجرد وسيلة للمماطلة.
Now,
الآن،
all my trusted aides
كل مساعديني الموثوق بهم
have perished.
لقد هلكوا.
Can you stay and help me?
هل يمكنك البقاء ومساعدتي؟
You can't even protect yourself now.
لا يمكنك حتى حماية نفسك الآن.
Only by reclaiming power
فقط من خلال استعادة السلطة
can I avenge wronged officials
هل يمكنني الانتقام من المسؤولين المظلومين؟
and the people of Pingxiang.
وشعب بينغشيانغ.
So you agree?
فهل أنت موافق؟
Why do you think
لماذا تعتقد
I'd cooperate with a philanderer?
هل سأتعاون مع زير نساء؟
That was an accident.
لقد كان حادثا.
Though I often mess with women,
على الرغم من أنني أتعامل مع النساء كثيرًا،
actually, I...
في الواقع، أنا...
Enough!
كافٍ!
Never mention it again.
لا تذكر ذلك مرة أخرى.
If you lay a finger on me again,
إذا وضعت إصبعك علي مرة أخرى،
I'll castrate you alive.
سأخصيك حيًا.
Okay.
تمام.
What's that smell on you?
ما هذه الرائحة عليك؟
Why so fragrant?
لماذا عطرة جداً؟
Marinated specially to kill you.
متبلة خصيصا لقتلك.
Now I've not only failed my mission,
الآن لم أفشل في مهمتي فحسب،
but also...
ولكن أيضا...
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
it was also my first time.
وكانت هذه المرة الأولى بالنسبة لي أيضًا.
Master,
يتقن،
Cheng Ge hasn't succeeded after days in the palace,
لم ينجح تشنغ جي بعد أيام في القصر،
nor has any message come back.
ولم تصل أي رسالة.
Could something have gone wrong?
هل من الممكن أن يكون هناك خطأ ما؟
Contact her.
اتصل بها.
Tell her to accelerate.
اطلب منها أن تسرع.
No more delays.
لا مزيد من التأخير.
Understood.
مفهومة.
(What am I doing?)
(ماذا أفعل؟)
(What has that)
(ما هذا)
(to do with me?)
(ماذا عني؟)
(I'm here)
(أنا هنا)
(bearing the grievances of Pingxiang's people.)
(تحمل مظالم شعب بينغشيانغ.)
(Cheng Ge,)
(تشنغ قه،)
(don't overthink.)
(لا تفكر كثيرًا.)
Who is Cheng Ge?
من هو تشنغ جي؟
Cheng Ge is rewarded with sea cucumber soup
تم مكافأة تشنغ جي بحساء خيار البحر
for meritorious service.
للخدمة الجليلة.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Look at the new waiting maid.
أنظر إلى الخادمة الجديدة المنتظرة.
How favored she is!
كم هي محظوظة!
Indeed.
بالفعل.
Why does she get such favor?
لماذا تحظى بمثل هذا الفضل؟
Who knows?
من يعلم؟
(Still seeking chances.)
(مازلت أبحث عن الفرص.)
(Something's off.)
(هناك شيء خاطئ.)
(The Emperor is a puppet.)
(الإمبراطور هو دمية.)
(Truth lies with another.)
(الحقيقة تكمن في الآخر.)
She dares disobey me!
إنها تجرؤ على عصياني!
Could this jeopardize your plan?
هل يمكن أن يعرض هذا خطتك للخطر؟
It seems I underestimated Shi Yu.
يبدو أنني قللت من شأن شي يو.
If someone else was behind Pingxiang rebellion
إذا كان هناك شخص آخر وراء تمرد بينغشيانغ
and the Pingxiang heirs
وورثة بينغشيانغ
in the weaving house learn of it,
في بيت النسيج تعلم ذلك،
will they still help us kill Shi Yu?
هل سيساعدوننا في قتل شي يو؟
Then we must act faster
إذن يجب علينا أن نتحرك بشكل أسرع
and eliminate Shi Yu soon,
والقضاء على شي يو قريبا،
in case this becomes complicated.
في حالة أصبح هذا الأمر معقدًا.
Then we...
ثم نحن...
Isn't there an alternative method?
هل هناك طريقة بديلة؟
Make preparations.
قم بالتحضيرات.
Understood.
مفهومة.
I'll do it myself.
سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Let me ask you.
دعني أسألك.
If the Prince Regent
إذا كان الأمير الوصي
truly massacred Pingxiang under your watch,
لقد ذبحت بينغشيانغ حقًا تحت إشرافك،
with all court officials observing,
مع مراقبة جميع مسؤولي المحكمة،
how could he deceive everyone?
كيف يمكنه أن يخدع الجميع؟
The Prince Regent has arrived.
لقد وصل الأمير الوصي.
See for yourself.
انظر بنفسك.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Lord Father, why are you here?
يا رب الآب لماذا أنت هنا؟
I was about to see you.
لقد كنت على وشك رؤيتك.
No need for formalities.
لا حاجة إلى أي إجراءات شكلية.
I know about your stay with the Empress last night.
أعلم عن إقامتك مع الإمبراطورة الليلة الماضية.
This marks a fresh start.
وهذا يمثل بداية جديدة.
You've done exceptionally well.
لقد قمت بعمل جيد بشكل استثنائي.
Your teachings
تعاليمك
are etched in my heart.
محفورة في قلبي.
What's delivered today
ما تم تسليمه اليوم
are medicinal tributes from foreign envoys.
هي هدايا طبية من مبعوثين أجانب.
May Your Majesty
رحمك الله
preserve your health.
حافظ على صحتك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
The Emperor prioritizes state affairs,
الإمبراطور يعطي الأولوية لشؤون الدولة،
continuing his lineage
استمرار نسبه
and securing the empire.
وتأمين الإمبراطورية.
The Prince Regent has great foresight.
يتمتع الأمير الوصي برؤية ثاقبة عظيمة.
Unity of wise ruler
وحدة الحاكم الحكيم
and loyal officials
والمسؤولين المخلصين
brings prosperity to the realm.
يجلب الرخاء إلى المملكة.
(The imperial seal)
(الختم الإمبراطوري)
(isn't with Shi Yu?)
(أليس مع شي يو؟)
Please take care.
من فضلك اعتني بنفسك.
I shall take my leave now.
سوف آخذ إجازتي الآن.
Good.
جيد.
Excellent!
ممتاز!
(If Prince Regent holds historians,)
(إذا كان الأمير ريجنت يحمل المؤرخين)
(wouldn't history be his to rewrite?)
(ألا يكون التاريخ من حقه أن يعيد كتابته؟)
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
I ask, you answer.
أنا أسأل، أنت تجيب.
Yes, yes.
نعم نعم.
Is the Pingxiang rebellion documented?
هل تم توثيق تمرد بينغشيانغ؟
It's Prince Regent's achievement.
إنه إنجاز الأمير ريجنت.
It must be documented.
يجب توثيقه.
Where to verify?
أين يمكن التحقق؟
Well...
حسنًا...
Think carefully.
فكر جيدا.
If even one word is a lie,
ولو كانت كلمة واحدة كذبة،
this dagger won't show mercy.
هذا الخنجر لن يظهر الرحمة.
I'll talk.
سأتحدث.
I'll speak.
سأتكلم.
Time?
وقت؟
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
it's already Hai hour.
لقد حانت الساعة بالفعل.
you should rest now.
ينبغي عليك الراحة الآن.
Why isn't she back yet?
لماذا لم تعود بعد؟
Who?
من؟
Y-Your Majesty,
ي-جلالتك،
where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Your Majesty!
جلالتك!
(Never imagined a mere Archives Room)
(لم أتخيل أبدًا مجرد غرفة أرشيف)
(would have such heavy security.)
(سيكون هناك مثل هذا الأمن الثقيل.)
(The Prince Regent)
(الأمير الوصي)
(has truly hidden)
(لقد أخفى حقا)
(many shameful secrets here.)
(هناك الكثير من الأسرار المخزية هنا.)
Changing guards!
تغيير الحرس!
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Where's Cheng Ge?
أين تشنغ جي؟
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
I haven't seen her for some time.
لم أرها منذ بعض الوقت.
♪Without fate, this dream would fade♪
♪بدون القدر، هذا الحلم سوف يتلاشى♪
♪Without you, my life would quietly end♪
♪بدونك، حياتي ستنتهي بهدوء♪
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
♪Let fate cut like a blade♪
♪دع القدر يقطع مثل الشفرة♪
♪I bid you one last farewell♪
♪أقول لك وداعا أخيرا♪
♪I know not love's emptiness nor hatred's pain♪
♪لا أعرف فراغ الحب ولا ألم الكراهية♪
♪When we meet again, the snow will melt away♪
♪عندما نلتقي مرة أخرى، سوف يذوب الثلج♪
♪One vow, so deep in love♪
♪عهد واحد، عميق في الحب♪
♪I'd give my life for it♪
♪سأعطي حياتي من أجله♪